(Penny:)Yeah, it's true.
Amy told me.
(Raj:)How did that even happen?
(Raj:)Did they know that's
what they were doing
(Raj:)when they were doing it?
(Penny:)I-I guess they just figured
it out at some point.
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Raj:)I can't believe old
Smelly Pooper finally got laid.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Hey.
(Leonard:)Hope you're hungry.
(Amy:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)A friendly sentiment
in this country,
(Sheldon:)cruel taunt in the Sudan.
(Sheldon:)It's a lesson in context.
(Leonard:)Will Amy be
joining us for dinner?
(Sheldon:)Yes, I believe so.
(Leonard:)Good, good.
(Raj:)Everything...
okay between you two?
(Greene:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Why do you ask?
(Leonard:)No reason.
(Leonard:)I was just talking to Raj,
(Leonard:)and he mentioned what a lovely
glow she has these days.